# Kishan Gujarati

React JS | React-Native

I'm a Web & Mobile App developer having a total of 5.9 years experience including 4 years of experience in React-Native and working Globally with Clients, Startups and Agencies. I design & develop compelling apps, intuitive interfaces, and engaging brands. I am willing to work as a key player in a challenging & creative environment. To make sincere and continuous efforts towards building a promising career, and to take challenges in life so that I can contribute to the growth and success of the organization, society and thus the whole nation.

**EXPERIENCE** 

## **Robosoft Technologies**, Bengaluru— Software Engineer

January 2023 - December 2023

- Responsible for developing UI pages using ReactJS, React-Native, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JSON
- Maintained the code using a version control system like Git.
- Developed Reusable components and workflows with basic auth and social auth for projects

## **Wedowebapps LLC**, Ahmedabad— *ReactNative Developer*

January 2020 - January 2023

- Responsible for developing UI pages using ReactJS, React-Native, NextJS, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery and JSON
- Used UI Router to create different hierarchy structure in single page application
- Used open source library like Material UI, Ant Design and Styled-Components to create customized components
- Maintained the code using a version control system like Git

## Quixom Technology, Ahmedabad— ReactJs Developer

January 2018 - November 2019

- Responsible for developing UI pages using ReactJS, React-Native, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery and JSON
- Maintained the code using a version control system like Git
- Managed application data with Redux.

Bengaluru, Karnataka India.

+91 9409258007

krushnagujarati@gmail.com

**PROFILES** 

LinkedIn

StackoverFlow

**SKILLS** 

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS & React-Native

Redux

Git

NodeJS (Beginner)

AWS (Beginner)

Roku (Beginner)

**LANGUAGES** 

English, Hindi, Gujarati

**EDUCATION** 

## Gujarat Technological University, Ahmedabad

Bachelor of Engineering (Computer)

2014 - 2018

#### **PROJECTS**

## BookingsAfrica — (Site, Android App, iOS App)

ReactJS + NextJS, React-Native, Redux, NodeJS (Under Development)

Bookingsafrica.com is a Pan African online marketplace that enables digital work physically & virtually. We facilitate seamless transactions between service providers, agencies and consumers from sourcing to payment in a way that is safe, transparent and cost effective for all users.

## Lordhair — (Site)

ReactJS, Magento 2, graphQL (Under Development)

Lordhair is an online retailer of hyper-realistic hair systems, hairpieces, toupees, wigs, and integration solutions. It provides wigs and hair solutions for Men, women and children. Also you can customize your wig as you want as it has customized your product option.

### Trade and Go— (Site)

ReactJS + NextJS, Redux

Trade and go is an Artificial intelligence based forex trading platform. Users can register with his broker account. Users can see the real time candle chart for the currencies and also there is custom AI based singling part from which they can book his maximum profit.

## EudaMed Scan— (Android App, iOS App)

React-Native

EUDAMED is the medical device database for the European Commission. You scan the human-readable string on a medical device label OR search using an individual UDI DI on screen/paper. It'll scan the code and show the Manufacturer details of the product.

# SafariBank— (<u>iOS App</u>)

React-Native, Redux

This is a full loan finance service at your fingertips with a super easy-to-use loan application interface featuring sliders to help you choose your loan amount and term. You get a decision in principle within minutes. Once approved you can access your finance within 24 hours.

#### Roku POC

Roku, BrightScript

Roku POC includes Markup list, Rowlist and Video Player functionality. This POC channel has some videos and a detailed page of videos. Also it has settings for changing the background of the channel.

# **Reusable Components**

ReactJS, Redux

Reusable components have some basic common components (form, input, button, etc.) for projects which can be used in other projects directly. It also includes some auth flows with implementation with API and social auth, which can be used in other projects directly.